翻译 根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
翻译 胡说大王
翻译 潇然
翻译 showeryhe
翻译 SophiaSaaaga
翻译 小酸奶
翻译 小泡椒
翻译 星星与野狗
时间轴 倩倩
时间轴 Poxle
校对 根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
后期&总监 灰灰是菇凉
西部世界
第一季  第四集
徳洛丽丝
Dolores?
在
Yes.
你知道你现在在哪儿吗
Do you know where you are?
我...
I...
我在梦里
I'm in a dream.
在此之前
Before this,
你知道发生了什么事吗
do you know what happened?
我的父母
My parents...
他们伤害了他们
They hurt them.
请控制下你的情绪反应
Limit your emotional affect, please.
接下来发生了什么
What happened next?
然后他们杀了他们
Then they killed them.
然后
And then...
我跑了
I ran.
我关心的人都不在了
Everyone I cared about is gone...
内心好痛苦
and it hurts...
撕心裂肺
so badly.
如果你愿意  我可以让那种感觉消失
I can make that feeling go away if you'd like.
我为什么要那样呢
Why would I want that?
那种痛
The pain,
失去他们
their loss...
是他们留给我唯一的东西了
it's all I have left of them.
你以为悲痛会让你的内心更弱小
You think the grief will make you smaller inside,
好像你的心彻底瓦解了  但其实并不会
like your heart will collapse in on itself, but it doesn't.
我觉得我内心又敞开了一片空间
I feel spaces opening up inside of me
就像一栋我从未探索过的带有很多房间的大楼
like a building with rooms I've never explored.
那很美  徳洛丽丝
That's very pretty, Dolores.
那是我们预先写好的程序吗
Did we write that for you?
部分是的
In part.
我改编自一段关于爱的有剧本对话
I adapted it from a scripted dialogue about love.
我现在的这些想法  有什么不对吗
Is there something wrong with these thoughts I'm having?
没有
No.
但真正做决定的人  并非只有我一个
But I'm not the only one making these decisions.
你能帮助我吗
Can you help me?
你想要什么
Well, what is it that you want?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是  这个世界...
But this world...
我觉得这个世界或许有什么不对劲
I think there may be something wrong with this world.
藏在表层之下的东西
Something hiding underneath.
要么是那个原因...
Either that or...
要么就是我有什么毛病
or there's something wrong with me.
我可能疯了
I may be losing my mind.
我想让你尝试一件事
There's something I'd like you to try.
是个游戏
It's a game.
一个秘密
A secret.
叫做...
It's called...
迷宫
the Maze.
是什么样的游戏
What kind of game is it?
是一种非常独特的游戏  徳洛丽丝
It's a very special kind of game, Dolores.
目标就是找到迷宫的中心
The goal is to find the center of it.
如果你能做到
If you can do that,
那或许你可以获得自由
then maybe you can be free.
我觉得...
I think...
我觉得我想获得自由
I think I want to be free.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在想什么
Penny for your thoughts.
你有没有遇到过  有时候话到嘴边却不记得了
Ever had something on the tip of your tongue,
你越是努力去想  就越是想不起来
but the harder you try to remember it, the more it slips away?
大多数触碰到我嘴边的东西
Most things that touch the tip of my tongue,
我都很乐意忘掉
I'm happy to forget.
除了那个来自阿比林的牛仔
Except that cowpoke from Abilene.
他胯下的那玩意儿
That thing he was packing--
我倒是终身难忘
that was something to remember.
我只记得  你给那个牛仔免单了
All I recall is you letting that cowpoke skip out on his bill.
天啊  我该付钱给他才对
Hell, I oughta been paying him.
他对那玩意儿的灵活使用简直...
The way he used that thing.
最好压一压他们的兴致
Better cool them off
否则他们就会从赌博嫖娼升级到更恶劣的行为
before they move from gambling and whoring
造成的破坏修复起来又要花很多钱
to sins that are more costly to repair.
怎么了  梅芙
What is the matter, Maeve?
你的眼睛里有什么东西
Something in your eye.
你他妈能杀了它吗
Aw, can you fucking kill it?
天啊
Jesus.
怎么耽误了这么久
What's the hold up?
我们要把那个放在下一趟运输车的最上层
We need that one on the next shuttle topside.
我还没处理完她  稍等
I'm not finished with her yet. Hang on.
她的腹部还有一颗子弹要取出来
I've got another bullet fragment to remove from her abdomen.
质保部要求将她立即送过去
QA wants her back on the floor now.
把她修补下  然后放到...
Just patch her and get her on the...
...触碰到我嘴边的东西
touch the tip of my tongue...
我都很乐意忘掉
I'm happy to forget.
除了那个来自阿比林的牛仔
Except that cowpoke from Abilene.
他胯下那玩意儿
That thing he was packing--
那倒是让我终身难忘
that was something to remember.
他对那玩意儿的灵活使用简直...
The way he used that thing.
不  我不会把这归为正常的接待员行为
No, I would not characterize this as normal host behavior.
但你将之描述成符合正常范围的
Yet you're describing it as within normal parameters.
它没有伤害我们
Well, it didn't hurt us.
它的行为很反常
Its behavior was unconventional.
它用一块石头砸碎了自己的脑袋
It smashed its own head in with a rock.
有可能只是其撒玛利亚人反射的表现
It is possible that it's a manifestation of its Samaritan reflex.
也有可能这种行为
And it's also possible that behavior
会为此类问题树立专有的解决办法
takes a proprietary approach to problems like this
在他们搞砸的时候  就可以不用承认了
to avoid having to admit when they fuck up.
知不知道它为什么会偏离循环
Do we have any idea what caused it to go off loop?
不知道  但我希望能
No, but I am hoping
恢复它的一些认知功能
to recover some of its cognition.
我们成功地
We managed to
在分解加剧之前  稳定了它的脑部
stabilize its wetware before there was too much decomposition.
你看
See?
有趣
Interesting.
到底能不能从这玩意中
Is there any hope of actually
提取出一些东西
extracting something from this?
-我们可以试试  -不行
- We can try. - No.
现在由我的团队接手调查
My team will take over the investigation now.
你的团队
Your team?
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
听着  这家伙连个揉成团的纸巾都打不开
Look, this guy couldn't debug a balled-up napkin.
如果你希望我们弄清楚到底出了什么问题
If-- if you would like us to figure out what went wrong here,
我们需要有获取的权限
we need to be allowed to access it.
没有第二次机会
No more second chances.
从今以后  质保部门会负责处理此类问题
QA will handle events like this from now on.
你有意见吗  伯纳德
Is that going to be a problem, Bernard?
我们都有很多工作要忙
We've all got plenty of work on our plates.
如果你们想接手这个  没问题
If you guys want to take this one, fine.
结束之后给我们一份调查报告就行
Just get us a copy of the postmortem when it's done.
开始吧
Let's get started.
我一直认为你给我这份工作
You know, I always figured you gave me this job
是因为我有话直说
because I speak my mind.
-是这样  -很好
- I did. - Good.
如果你一出现就直接屈服
I would've preferred you not show up at all
我希望你还是别出现为好
if the first thing you were going to do is cave.
-他们认为我们有所隐瞒  -我们没有啊
- They think we're not telling them something. - And we're not!
现在明显出现了一种行为模式
There is clearly a pattern of behavior here.
最早是艾伯纳西  现在又来一个
First there was Abernathy, and now there's this.
我见过出现幻听的接待员  还有爬上山顶
I mean, I've got hosts imagining voices and climbing mountaintops
去研究星象图的
to consult their astrological chart.
这不是什么小故障
This is not a fucking glitch.
不知道为什么  你不想让我告诉别人
And for some reason, you don't want me to tell anyone.
好像除了我之外  这里所有人
It is like everybody around here
都在打着自己的小算盘
has got some kind of fucking agenda except for me.
还有...怎么了
And-- what?
我记得我刚开始在这里工作的时候
I remember when I first started here.
接待员看起来都栩栩如生
The hosts seemed very lifelike.
你会开始对他们的行为进行过度解读
You begin to read things into their behaviors.
-别一副高高在上的样子  -好吧
- Don't be patronizing. - Fine.
接待员不会想象  但你会
The hosts don't imagine things, you do.
那不是猎户座
That's not Orion.
猎户座腰带上只有三颗星  不是四颗
There are three stars in Orion's Belt, not four.
你一定很冷吧
You must be cold.
穿上这个
Take that.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
我们得带她回甜水镇
We gotta take her back to Sweetwater.
你开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding?
罗根  你知道她不属于这外面的世界
Come on, Logan, you know she doesn't belong out here.
你如果现在走了  那个亡命之徒斯利姆·米勒
You leave now, that no-good outlaw Slim Miller
肯定就抓不到了
is sure to evade our grasp.
没门
No fucking way.
是你带我来当这个傻逼赏金猎人的
You were the one who dragged me on this stupid bounty hunt.
至少我们得把这件事做完
The least we're going to do is see it through, okay?
我们不能带着她追捕犯人
We can't take her on a bounty hunt.
如果你这么担心她
If you're so concerned about her well-being,
那我一枪爆了她的头就好了
I'll just blow her brains out,
园区会派人来回收她
and then the park will come get her.
你能不能别总想着杀人操逼
Can you please stop trying to just kill or fuck everything?
我懂了
Now I get it.
怎么
What?
园区派她过来  好让你终于
The park sent her so that you will finally
能对某件事上心
have something to give a shit about.
是啊  控制中心的人肯定是
Oh, yeah, I'm sure the people at the controls
时刻监视着我的情绪
are monitoring my every mood.
他们就是这么做的
That's exactly what they're doing.
拜托  难道你认为
Come on, you really think it's a coincidence
你在甜水镇唯一会报以微笑的人
that the only thing that you even smiled at back in Sweetwater
就这么出现在你面前只是个巧合吗
just happened to drop into your lap?
这就是公司为什么想对这里增持股份的原因
This is why the company needs to bump our stake in this place.
他们能让你拥有使命感
They can even give you a sense of purpose.
你说这趟旅程是为了欢迎我加入你们家族
You said the trip was about welcoming me to the family.
其实是公事吗
This is business?
威廉  对我们家族而言  所有事都是公事
With our family, William, everything is business.
我们得继续前进了  先生们
We better get a move on, gentlemen.
应该就是这里了  劳伦斯
This should be the place, Lawrence.
血河
The Blood Arroyo.
有很多蛇  但都不会生蛋
Plenty of snakes, but none of the egg-laying variety.
你杀了我妻子
You killed my wife,
杀了我家族的一群人
severely pruned my family tree
就为了找个什么迷宫
all in pursuit of some goddamn maze.
你到底想找什么
The hell you hope to find, anyway?
这整个世界就是一个故事
This whole world is a story.
我每页都读过  除了最后一页
I've read every page except the last one.
我得搞清楚结局如何
I need to find out how it ends.
想要知道这一切意义何在
I want to know what this all means.
瞧  这就是为什么我一直没念书识字
See, now that's why I never learned to read.
我们何不忘了那条该死的蛇
Why don't we forget about this damn snake,
赶紧去珀里亚
head to Pariah?
我在那儿的朋友能帮我们
My friends there can help us.
你朋友那没有我要找的东西
Well, your friends have nothing I'm looking for,
这趟旅程没有
not this trip.
再说了
Besides...
我们还是找到那条蛇了
I think we found our snake after all.
真可耻
Shame on you.
你昨天还是有妇之夫
You were a married man up until yesterday.
她吗  不可能
Her? Hell, no.
我喜欢有点泼辣的女人
I like a little fire in my women.
她上过的
The only thing she's ever mounted
恐怕只有死人
are dead heads on sticks.
我们应该快点离开
We should get the fuck out of--
给我们的马又找到不少食物
We found some more food for the horses.
很好
Good.
它们饿得都变得脾气很暴躁
They were starting to get ornery.
我和朋友只是在欣赏你的纹身
My friend and I were just admiring your tattoo.
我们想知道其背后的故事
We'd love to know the story behind it.
我喜欢你的帽子
I like your hat.
也许我会把它留下
Maybe I'll keep it.
剩下的都喂马吧
The horses can have the rest of you.
我们为何从未谋面
How in hell have we never met?
很明显是我的疏忽
Clearly a terrible oversight on my part.
能问一句  你前往何处吗
Where, may I ask, are you headed?
去拿回一些有价值的东西
To retrieve something of great value.
看来你有点人手不足
You look a little shorthanded.
我们人手很充足
We got enough men.
看来你有人手空缺了
Seems like you got a couple positions open.
有一个接待员严重脱离了她的循环
We've got a host making a pretty big deviation from her loop.
-哪个  -甜水镇农场主的女儿
- Which one? - The rancher's daughter from Sweetwater.
德洛丽丝
Dolores.
-她在陪游客吗  -不清楚
- Is she accompanying a guest? - Unclear.
老板的新故事线
The boss is disrupting so many storylines
打乱了很多情节  所以很难说
with his new narrative, it's hard to tell.
把她标记给行为部门
Flag her with behavior.
他们今天就能把她拉出来
They can pull her today.
确保一切如常
Make sure everything's checking out.
早上好
Good morning.
这镇子真漂亮  这是你的家乡吗
It's a lovely town. Is this your home?
你来自哪里
Well, where are you from?
和你一样
Same as you.
你不记得了吗
Don't you remember?
记起来
Remember.
女士
Ma'am?
听说艾伯纳西农场有个女孩失踪了
Got word a girl went missing from Abernathy Ranch.
你是来自那里吗
Is that where you belong?
你爸爸肯定很担心你
I'm sure your daddy's worried about you.
我父亲死了
My father's dead.
我不要回去
I'm not going back.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
只是在帮助一个迷路的游人
Oh, just helping a lost traveler.
她没迷路  她是跟我一起的
She's not lost, she's with me.
抱歉
My mistake.
-祝你们早安  -谢了
- Y'all have a nice morning. - Yeah.
我们有关于斯利姆的线索了
So, we got a lead on Slim.
如果你愿意  可以留在这里
You can stay here if you want,
我到时候折返回来接你
and I'll just circle back and get you.
不  我觉得自己需要继续走下去
No, I think I need to keep going.
好吧
Okay.
看来她需要确保
Apparently, she needs to make certain
他们要找的东西在他们认为的那个地方
this thing they're looking for is where they think it is.
她说如果消息没问题  就给我们信号
She said she'd signal if the information was good.
看来这就是信号了
Guess that's the signal.
很抱歉给你和朋友带来了不便
I'm sorry if I caused trouble with you and your friend.
没有  没有  没关系
Oh, no, no. No, it's fine.
我很高兴你找到了我们
I'm glad you found us.
我还没问你要去哪
I didn't get a chance to ask where you're headed.
我还不知道
I don't really know yet.
我还以为他们会把你们放在特定的地区或者路上
I guess I figured they kept you in zones or on paths or...
我以前相信每个人都有自己的路
I used to believe there was a path for everyone.
现在我发现自己从未想过
Now I think I never asked
那条路会把我带往何方
where that path was taking me.
我们会在秋天把牲口赶下山
We would bring the herd down off the mountain in the fall.
有时我们会在路上弄丢一只
Sometimes we would lose one along the way,
我会很担心
and I'd worry over it.
我父亲
My father...
我父亲会告诉我
My father would tell me...
它们自会找到回家的路
that the steer would find its own way home.
通常  它们都会回来
And, often as not, they did.
我从未想过
Never occurred to me that
我们带它们回来是为了屠宰
we were bring them back for the slaughter.
你现在要怎样找到自己的路
How are you going to find your way now?
我觉得你或许不会明白
I'm not sure you'll understand.
有时我感觉
Sometimes I feel...
有什么东西在呼唤我
like something's calling me.
告诉我在这以外
Telling me there's a place for me
有个地方在等我
somewhere beyond all this.
我明白这种感觉  德洛丽丝
Oh, I know that feeling, Dolores.
我明白这种感觉
I know that feeling.
但你真的不想回归以前的生活吗
But you really don't want to go back to your old life?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
You all right?
我打了个寒颤
I just got a chill.
仅此而已
That's all.
那我们还是回篝火边坐着
Let's-- let's go back to the fire.
你该是累坏了
You're probably exhausted.
-直接跟他说  -好
- Just talk to him. - All right.
打扰了  先生
Uh, excuse me, sir?
恕我冒昧打扰  但我必须说
I didn't want to intrude, but I just had to say
我十分敬仰您
that I'm such an admirer of yours.
您设的基金救了我妹妹的...
Your foundation literally saved my sister's--
再说一个字我就割开你的喉咙
One more word and I'll cut your throat.
明白了吗
Understand?
我他妈是来度假的
This is my fucking vacation.
显然  他们要找的东西在欧哈监狱
Apparently, whatever they're looking for is in the Ojal prison.
这些疯子计划从北方军骑兵队手里
These lunatics plan to steal a cannon
偷走一门大炮
from the Union cavalry unit.
炸出一条路杀进去
Blast their way in.
我没时间玩这么幼稚的游戏
I don't have time for color-by-numbers bullshit.
我天一亮就出发
I'll ride at dawn.
你想要什么  我会从监狱弄出来
I'll go get whatever you want out of that prison
亲自带给你
and bring it back myself.
前提是你能活着出来
Suppose you make it out alive.
你开价多少
What's your price?
只要几个字
Nothing but a few words.
第一时间下载无删减美剧  必须登录字幕组网站www.zimuzu.tv
我想知道你纹身背后的故事
I want the story behind your tattoo.
你为什么会有兴趣
What's your interest in it?
你听说过一个叫阿诺德的人吗
You ever heard of a man named Arnold?
他算是最早在这些地方定居的人
You could say he was the original settler of these parts.
他创造了一个供人们为所欲为的世界
He created a world where you could do anything you want,
www.zimuzu.tv  更好更快的原创翻译 双语字幕
除了一件事
except one thing--
你在这里死不了
you can't die.
也就是说无论这个世界多么接近真实
Which means no matter how real this world seems,
仍然不过是场游戏
it's still just a game.
但后来阿诺德打破了自己定下的规矩
But then Arnold went and broke his own rule.
他就死在这座乐园里
He died right here in the park.
但我相信他还有一个故事剩下没讲
Except I believe he had one story left to tell.
一个充满真正的危险和暴力的故事
A story with real stakes, real violence.
可以说我来这里是为了尊崇他的遗志
You could say I'm here to honor his legacy.
我认为你身上的纹身
And I think your tattoo
谜局的下一部分
is the next piece of the puzzle.
你愿意赌吗
So, do we have a wager?
你要闯进监狱
You aim to break into a prison
独自带出20个人
and take out 20 men alone?
不是独自
Not alone.
我要带上这位劳伦斯
I'll take Lawrence here.
我还需要一根火柴
And I'll need one match.
一根火柴
One match,
一把手枪  加一个白痴
one pistol, and one idiot.
我愿意赌一把
I'll take those odds.
你打算这一路上都对我沉默以对吗
You gonna give me the silent treatment the whole way there?
你本该任我被绞死
You should've left me hanging from those gallows.
至少我还能安详地死去
At least I could've died in peace
不用忍受你的抱怨
without having to hear you yammer.
我猜你没火吧
Don't suppose you have a light?
车里禁止抽烟
No smoking in here.
通常情况下  那当然
Normally, I'm sure,
但这是你能抽到的最好的烟草
but this is the finest tobacco a man can enjoy.
在外国妞儿丰腴的大腿上用手卷成
Hand-rolled on the ample thighs of exotic women.
或许你也该试试
Perhaps you'd like to try one yourself.
选择  劳伦斯
Choices, Lawrence.
你对自己说
You know, you tell yourself
你现在就像是我案板上的鱼肉
you've been at the mercy of mine
因为这样你就不用费心为自己考虑
because it spares you consideration of your own.
因为如果你真的考虑过自己的选择
Because if you did consider your choices,
你将不得不面对一个
you'd be confronted with a truth
你无法理解的真相
you could not comprehend--
你做出的选择都并非自主选择
that no choice you ever made was your own.
你一直都是个囚犯
You have always been a prisoner.
如果我告诉你  我是来释放你的呢
What if I told you I'm here to set you free?
走吧
Let's go!
偷马贼
Horse thieves.
该死的白痴  几乎当着我们的面开枪打死了几个人
Damn fools shot up a couple of pokes practically in front of us.
我见到的唯一一个白痴
Well, the only fool I see
就是站在我面前的这位
is the one standing right in front of me.
警官  你拘捕了
Deputy, you have there in your custody
三地最大的通缉犯
the most wanted man in three territories--
劳伦斯·佩德罗·马里亚·冈萨雷斯
Lawrence Pedro Maria Gonzalez.
我听说你法场脱身的事了
Heard you slipped the rope.
还害死了几个好人
Dropped some damn good men in exchange.
他的说法是
The way he tells it,
他更喜欢被行刑队执行枪决
he's more partial to a firing squad.
我们很乐意成全
I reckon we'll be happy to oblige.
我他妈要杀了你
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
或许等将来吧
Maybe someday.
把他和那个人关一起
Lock him up with the other man.
享受雪茄
Enjoy the cigars.
去你妈的
Go fuck yourself.
你是谁
And just who are you supposed to be?
你的救命恩人
Your salvation.
我想我们之前没见过吧
I don't believe we've ever met.
没错  确实没有
No, we haven't.
你一直以来似乎都是个...
You know, you always seemed like a--
经过市场检验的东西
a market-tested kind of thing.
一杆大枪  优美的疤痕
Big gun, tasteful scar.
受限于自己的小小圈子
Locked in your little cycle
像追自己尾巴的珍贵狮子狗
like a prized poodle after its own tail.
你听起来好像是
You sound like a man who's grown tired
活的不耐烦了
of wearing his guts on the inside.
没必要这么生气
There's no need to get testy.
我只是对你的世界观很好奇
I'm just curious about your worldview.
某种半土著的乱七八糟的东西吗
Some kind of half-native mumbo jumbo?
很简单
It's simple.
我认为只有真正的勇者
I believe that only the truly brave
才敢于正视这个世界  并明白世间的一切...
can look at the world and understand that all of it--
无论是神或是人
gods, men,
还有其他一切  都终将以悲剧收尾
everything else-- will end badly.
没人可以被拯救
No one will be saved.
那或许我们的共同点比我想的要多
Maybe we've got more in common than I thought.
那你呢
What about you?
怎样的命运转折让你流落至此
What turns of fate have brought you here?
说来话长
It's a long story.
我们没那个闲工夫
And we don't have the time.
可惜我们的时间可比你那朋友多
Got more time than your friend, sadly.
再过几天  我的朋友们就会来救我
It will be a few more days before my friends show up.
三天
Three days.
通常情况下
Normally.
恐怕我等不及了
I'm afraid I don't have time for that,
所以我们现在就走吧
so we're leaving now.
收到制造烟火效果的请求
I've got a request for a pyrotechnic effect.
恶魔  低当量  两个装药
Los Diablos, low-yield, two charges.
批准
Approved.
正在授权
Authorizing.
跟上  赫克托
Step lively, Hector.
有遗言吗
Any last words?
赶紧动手吧
Get it over with.
我操
Motherfucker.
一根火柴
One match.
你很有能力
You're a capable man.
我们去的地方你能帮上忙
We could do with your help where we're going.
恐怕不行
Afraid not.
我们欠你个人情
We owe you a debt.
不  你这位朋友
No, your friend here
只欠我一两句话
simply owes me a word or two.
说出来就行了
That'll do.
给个建议...
And a word of advice--
你们要找的东西
that thing you're looking for?
是不可能在那个保险箱里是找到的
You're never gonna find it in that safe.
他们闯进我们镇子时我才7岁
I was seven when they rode into my town.
有着魔鬼犄角  带着面具的人
Masked men in devils' horns.
他们杀光所有人...
They killed everyone--
妇女  幼童  连牲口都不放过
women, children, even the animals.
他们把我母亲从下巴劈开到裆部
They gutted my mother from her jaw to her sex.
我不得不把她温热的鲜血
I had to paint her warm blood
涂满我的全身
over my skin to make sure
让他们以为我死了
that they would think I was dead.
我长大后开始追杀他们
Every one of them I tracked down,
我会把死在我手下之人的血再次涂满全身
I used their blood to paint my skin again.
只剩下一个人
Only one man left.
蛇头
The head of the snake.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
他有很多名字
He has many names.
大多数人叫他怀亚特
Most know him as Wyatt.
等等  小姑娘  这...这是什么
Hey, little girl, what-- what is this?
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
别白费口舌了  女士
Don't waste your breath, lady.
那属于他们所谓的宗教
That thing's part of their so-called religion.
没人会告诉你的
Ain't none of them's gonna tell you nothing about that.
一小时5块钱
It's $5 for an hour,
要是你先洗澡就4块
4 if you bathe first.
如果我们只点一个
Well, if we just get the one,
那我第二个上  能不能打个折
do I get a discount for being second and all?
我想我们能商量出解决办法的
I'm sure we can work something out.
来吧
Come on.
那个高个子  我以前见过他
The tall one, I've seen him before,
他的画像贴在邮局窗口
hanging in the window of the post office.
土匪吗
Bandits?
你觉得他们来是有目的的吗
Do you think they're here for something?
我觉得他们可不仅仅是来操女人的
I think they're interested in more than a turn at Franny's backside.
我觉得他是赫克托的同伙
I think he rides with Hector.
传闻跟野蛮人一起生活的就是他吗
Is that the one they say lives out with the savages?
就是他
That's the one.
要走了吗  我才刚到呢
Taking off? I just got here.
你已经给了我需要的
You gave me what I needed.
我就是这个作用吗
So, is that all I'm good for?
帮你缓解压力
Letting off a little stress?
谁说我有压力了
Who says I'm stressed?
你表现得挺明显了
You have your tells.
是啊  伯纳德
Oh, yes, Bernard,
观察大师
master of observation.
明天我得找福特谈谈
Tomorrow I have to talk to Ford.
为什么
Why?
他在园区制造混乱
He's creating chaos in the park.
董事会的人随时会来
And the board will be descending at any moment.
我需要争取点时间
I need to buy some time.
要我给点建议吗
Some advice?
最好不要让他发现你很紧张或有防御性
Best to not show him you're nervous or defensive.
我没有什么好防御的
I have nothing to be defensive about.
那就不要交叉双臂
Then don't cross your arms.
这是一种古老的直觉
It's an ancient instinct.
任何动物的肚子都是最脆弱的地方
The belly is the most vulnerable part of every animal.
把我比作惊恐的野兽  竟然还挺性感的
It's so sexy being compared to a frightened beast.
这就对了
There.
这才是你该有的姿态
That's the posture you're looking for.
有时候
Sometimes,
尽管你尽了最大的努力
despite your best efforts,
你其实本来就那么迷人
you can actually be quite charming.
邻居来投诉了吗
Have the neighbors complained?
应该说  他们在问各种问题
Safe to say, they're asking questions.
虽然这些石头很难移开
The rocks would prefer not to move,
但我们还是要把它们清除
but we shall move them yet.
也许我能帮帮你
Perhaps I can help you with that.
你现在开发的故事线
The narrative you're creating
肯定是一项大工程
is clearly a massive endeavor.
如果你需要更多时间
If you need more time,
我觉得董事会肯定会乐意照顾一下
I'm sure the board would be happy to oblige.
他们肯定更加乐意
I'm sure they'd be happier
让我无限期推迟
for me to delay it indefinitely.
跟我来
Come with me.
你觉得我疯了
You imagine I have gone mad...
对吗
do you?
失去了理智
Lost my way?
我们只是担心
We're simply concerned
你即将带来的改变程度过大
about the extent of the changes you're making.
我们想保护你的遗产
We want to protect your legacy.
我的遗产
My legacy?
你不是很喜欢这个地方  对吗
You don't like this place very much, do you?
多年来  我见过很多你这样的人来来去去
I've seen many of you come and go over the years,
我能看出谁喜欢这里
and I can tell the ones who enjoy their time here
而谁不喜欢
and the ones who don't.
我挺欣赏的
I admire it,
这里的大胆风格
the audacity of it.
我都忘了这里有多美
I've forgotten how beautiful it is.
我小时候跟父母来过一次
I came here once as a child with my parents.
我觉得我们甚至就在这张桌子边坐过
I think we even sat at this table.
也许...也许是那张
Or maybe-- maybe that one.
我开始在这里工作时
When I started working here,
我意识到我不会喜欢这个地方
I realized this place wasn't something I would enjoy.
一开始  我想象一切都会
In the beginning, I imagined things would be
非常平衡
perfectly balanced.
我甚至为此和我的搭档阿诺德打赌
Even had a bet with my partner, Arnold, to that effect.
我们编了一百条充满希望的故事线
We made a hundred hopeful storylines.
当然了  几乎没人接受那些
Of course, almost no one took us up on them.
我输了
I lost the bet.
阿诺德总是对人类抱有一些阴暗的看法
Arnold always held a somewhat dim view of people.
他更喜欢接待员
He preferred the hosts.
他求我不要引入你们这些人
He begged me to not let you people in,
那些投资者
the moneymen.
像提洛岛一样
Delos.
但我告诉他我们会没事的
But I told him we'd be fine,
你们并不知道你们所花的钱  是用来建设什么了
that you didn't understand what you were paying for.
不是什么商业投机  不是什么主题公园
It's not a business venture, not a theme park,
而是一整个世界
but an entire world.
每一分一毫都是我们设计的
We designed every inch of it.
每片草叶
Every blade of grass.
在这里  我们就是神
In here, we were gods.
你们只是我们的客人
And you were merely our guests.
那阿诺德结局如何呢
And how did that work out for Arnold?
很不幸  他丧失了远见
Sadly, he lost his perspective.
他疯了
He went mad.
我没有  你也清楚
I haven't, as you well know.
我看事情  一直非常清楚透彻
I have always seen things very clearly.
我和我父母当年就坐在这张桌子边
This is the table I sat at with my parents.
我就坐在这张椅子上
This is the chair I sat in.
我们对客人了如指掌  不是吗
We know everything about our guests, don't we?
我们对我们的员工也是如此
As we know everything about our employees.
我希望你小心伯纳德
I do hope you will be careful with Bernard.
他的性情很敏感
He has a sensitive disposition.
非常抱歉  小姐
I beg your pardon, señorita.
这些年来有很多你这样的人
There have been many of you over the years,
我们一直  几乎一直
and we have always-- almost always
都能想办法解决
found a way to make it work.
所以  我客气地请求你
So, I will ask you nicely,
请你
please...
不要挡我的道
don't get in my way.
董事会会同意我的意见
The board will agree with me.
他们会派代表来
They'll be sending a representative.
但他们已经派人来了
But they already have.
我以为他们会告诉你呢
I thought they would've told you.
不用了  摩奴
That won't be necessary, Manu.
不用再来了
Not anymore.
你可以和其他人一起走了
You can join the others.
你可以告诉董事会
You can tell the board that
我会及时完成我的故事线
my narrative will be completed on time,
不会是怀旧的风格
and it won't be a retrospective,
我相信你们都恐惧会是那样
as I'm sure you have all feared.
我不是多愁善感之人
I'm not the sentimental type.
霍尔登说斯利姆带了一大帮手下
Holden says this Slim's got a whole gang with him,
所以我要你留在这里
so I need you to stay here.
如果你们寡不敌众
If you're outnumbered,
最不该的就是让一个人袖手旁观
the last thing you need is somebody standing by.
-我可以帮忙  -不  不  不
- I can help. - No, no, no.
我知道你也许不懂
I know it doesn't make any sense to you,
但我在这不会受伤  而你却会
but I can't get hurt in there, but you can.
我不想看到你受伤
I would hate to see that happen.
待在这里  好吗  注意安全
Just stay here. Okay? Be safe.
-你享受到告别之吻了吗  -闭嘴
- Did you get a good-bye kiss? - Shut up.
说真的  如果明天之前你还没上她
Seriously, if you don't bang her by tomorrow,
-她就归我了  -好了  听着
- I'm calling dibs. - Okay, listen up.
一会儿场面会非常混乱
It's gonna be a bag of nails in there.
斯利姆和他的手下人数太多
Slim and his boys got us outnumbered.
最关键的是  这地方是由一个家庭经营的
On top of that, there's a family runs this place.
善良的人
Good people.
我们必须确保那狼心狗肺的混蛋
We need to make sure that snake-hearted son of a bitch
-没有试图...  -是是是  懂
- doesn't try to-- - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
冒险  赏金  我们懂的
Risk, reward. We got it.
来吧  我们把这些混蛋杀个爽
Come on. Let's go fuck these fuckers up.
那他妈是什么
The fuck is that?
-你看我像条狗吗  -不  先生
- I look like a dog to you? - No, sir.
拿这些喂狗去吧
Feed that to them.
该拔枪了  狗杂种
Slap leather, cocksuckers.
老天
Oh, God!
我告诉过你的  对吧
Did I fucking tell you, or what?
升级版
Upgrade.
真棒
Nice.
不是我爱抱怨  但这真是鲁莽的行为
Ain't normally the type to complain, but this is just foolhardy.
两个人去和怀亚特较量
Two men taking on Wyatt.
你再多嘴  我就把马收回  劳伦斯
Keep talking, and I'm gonna take the horse back, Lawrence.
怀亚特手下的怪胎们刚刚消灭了上一支
Wyatt's freaks just wiped out the last group
前去搜寻他的小队
that went seeking him out.
而现在我们正骑马跟踪他
And here we are riding right after him.
我只是想说服你
I'm just trying to convince you
别让我俩像个局外人一样被杀死
not to get yourself and me as a bystander killed.
我不会让自己被杀
I'm not gonna get myself killed.
别以为我没听出这其中的差别
Don't think I didn't notice that distinction.
看来怀亚特的手下还留下了一人
Looks like Wyatt's men left somebody behind after all.
泰迪
Teddy.
我早该猜到的
I should've guessed.
求你  结束我的痛苦吧
Please, put me out of my misery.
不好意思  泰迪
I'm sorry, Teddy.
似乎你只剩痛苦了
It looks like misery's all you got.
放我下来  该死的
Let me out of this, God damn it!
通缉令上写着无论死活  对吧
That reward is dead or alive, right?
最好还是活着带回去
Always best to bring them in alive.
至少塞上他的嘴
Can we at least gag him?
好主意
That's a fine idea.
别这样
Aw, come on.
听着  我知道你们是为了赏金
Look, I-- I know you're in it for the money.
你们不是真正的执法者
You ain't no real lawman.
闭嘴
Shut up, you.
我老板埃尔·拉佐
Look, my boss, El Lazo,
他付你的钱  会比治安官给的多一倍
he'll pay you twice what the marshals will
只要你给我解绑把我送去珀里亚就行
if you cut me loose and get me to Pariah.
给我听好了  你个下贱的混球
Listen to me, you lowdown piece of dirt.
这些人是不会
These men won't--
-你他妈搞什么  -放轻松  兄弟
- What the fuck?! - Relax, man.
你不知道我们有多幸运
You have no idea how lucky we just got.
幸运  你刚打死了一个无辜的人
Lucky? You just shot an innocent man.
不  他是个机器人  和她还有斯利姆一样
No, he's a robot, just like her and just like Slim here,
不过斯利姆是埃尔·拉佐的手下
except that Slim works for El Lazo,
而埃尔·拉佐则是享受公园最高刺激的入场券
and El Lazo is our ticket to the best ride in the park.
你的傻逼任务把我们引向了一个复活节彩蛋
Your bullshit mission led us right to an Easter egg.
你不能放他走
You're not going to let him go.
瞧瞧你
Well, well. Look at you.
我对你越发感兴趣了  农场女
You're starting to grow on me, farm girl.
给我让开
Now, out of the way.
你敢
Don't you dare.
瞧吧
See?
多有趣啊  现在我们都拿枪对准一个人质
This is gonna be fun! Now we're each gonna have one.
我也不会操我的人质
I won't fuck mine either.
你真令人恶心
You're disgusting.
只是个小嗜好
Just an acquired taste.
你会慢慢爱上我的  我保证
You're gonna grow to love me, I promise.
好了  行吧
Come on. Hmm?
拜托
Come on.
跟我一起当坏人吧
Go black hat with me.
来吧  你要去拯救这女孩
Come on, you got to, you know, save the girl.
现在该给我找点事做
Now give me a little something.
你什么毛病
What is your problem?
我们一脱离现实世界
The second we get away from the real world,
你就变成一个邪恶的混蛋了
you turn into an evil prick.
邪恶吗
Evil?
这他妈是个游戏啊  比利
It's a fucking game, Billy!
-别叫我比利  -你还想赢得她的芳心吗
- Don't call me Billy! - Are you still trying to impress her?
因为我保证她根本毫不在意
Because I guarantee she does not give a shit
你怎么玩这场游戏
about how you play this game.
对吧  德洛丽丝
Do you, Dolores?
他在说什么  威廉
What's he talking about, William?
来一趟黑暗之旅  她是不会有事的
She will be just fine with a trip down the dark side.
你也不会有事的
And so will you.
相信我
Trust me.
所以珀里亚怎么走
So, which way to Pariah?
接下来交给我就行了
Oh, you just let me take it from here.
好  好戏要来了
All right, time for the floor show.
这次有几位客人是赫克托的随行
Got some guests riding with Hector this time.
给他们点靶子
Let's give them something to shoot at.
给几个士兵重置任务
Retask a few of those soldiers.
如果你带着一群携带武器的人
If you're riding into our town
骑进我们的小城
under the company of armed men,
你需要报上你此行所为何事
you'll need to state your business.
大破坏
Mayhem.
你好啊
Well, hello there.
我想谈谈
I want to talk.
用这种方式找人谈谈还真有意思
Interesting way of starting a conversation.
今天就是个有趣的日子
Oh, it's an interesting kind of day.
我可爱的朋友
Now, my lovely friend,
你想做什么交易
what deal is it you want to make?
你来取保险柜里的东西
You're here for what's in the safe.
你怎么知道的
Now, how would you know that?
我一眼就能看出想要特殊服务的男人
I can always tell when a man wants something that's not on the menu.
我会给你密码
I'll give you the combination
以此交换一些答案
in exchange for some answers.
你觉得我有你要的答案
You assume I have any answers.
这世界疯了
This world is madness.
我要了解关于这个的事情
I want to know about this.
有几个在农场的家庭
I've got a couple families in the homestead
改了他们的既定活动
who changed their itinerary.
他们要进城了
They're headed into town.
应该20分钟左右到
Should be there in 20 minutes or so.
那地方血流成河
The place is a bloodbath.
行
Fine.
阻止他们
Cut these guys off.
让他们的武器卡壳  派出骑兵队
Jam their weapons and send in the cavalry.
该死
Oh, shit.
我们把他们在监狱里关一个晚上
We'll give them a night in lockup,
然后让一名马里波萨的女孩
then have one of the girls at the Mariposa
把钥匙藏在早饭里带给他们
bring them a key hidden in their breakfast.
一旦客人们安置好了  我们来清场
If the guests are squared away, let's wrap it up.
这是暗影
This is a shade.
神圣的本地传说
Sacred native lore.
他们会做这种小人
They make figures of them.
60.
暗影是做什么的
And what does the shade do?
你见过暗影吗
You've seen this?
是什么
What is it?
跨越世界的人
The man who walks between worlds.
他们从地狱被派来监督我们的世界
They were sent from hell to oversee our world.
47.
这是你对我最后的要求吗
Is this the last thing you required of me?
因为我们需要的时间
'Cause we need a little more time
比警队会给的要长一些
than the constabulary will allow.
亲爱的  如果我对你有这种兴趣
Sweetheart, if I took that manner of interest in you,
可轮不到你说我们需要多久
you'd have no say in how long we'd need whatsoever.
我以为我疯了
I thought I was crazy,
我之前中了枪
but I got shot...
在这里
here.
没有伤痕
There's no wound.
没有  但我确实中枪了
No, but I was shot.
这东西站在我面前
And this was standing over me.
然后一切就像没发生过一样
And then it was as if it never happened.
我要你切开这里
I want you to cut me right there.
我不喜欢将手无寸铁的女人开膛破肚
I'm not in the habit of cutting into defenseless women.
你也有脸当邪恶歹徒
Some big, bad outlaw.
梦游者说有些人能看到他们
The Dreamwalker said there were some who could see them.
-那是上天的恩赐  -恩赐
- That it's a blessing from God. - A blessing?
能看到操控你的主人们
To see the masters who pull your strings.
他们不知道他们在说什么
They don't know what they're talking about.
你想躺着死
You'd rather die lying down or...
还是站着死
up on your feet?
去死吧
Go to hell.
来吧
Go on, then.
这可是头一次
This would be the first goddamn time
我连续两次求一个男人对我动手
I've had to ask a man to put his hands on me twice.
开门  艾斯卡顿  不然我们就开枪了
Open up, Escaton, or we'll fire.
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
说明我没有疯
That I'm not crazy after all.
最后一次机会了  艾斯卡顿
Last chance, Escaton!
出来投降  不然我们就开枪了
Come out or we're shooting!
还有这一切都无所谓
And that none of this matters.